Damini Sharma

UI/Visual Designer

I am an ambitious UI/Visual Designer that pays close attention to detail. I have 2 years of experience in UI design, user research, wireframing, and, most importantly, UI/Visual Designing. Able to solve problems, manage projects, and communicate with stakeholders both inside and outside the company.

Professional Experience

Cloud Engineer

Cloudxchange.io | 2024 - Present

- I work on a customized monitoring technology as well as dedicated teams 24 hours a day, seven days a week
- Manage all data privacy, servers, and other AWS services as well.

Visual Designer

RECZEE Freelance | 2022 - 2024

- My role was to create a seamless Interactive Website Design with Prototypes and Wireframes.
- Collaboration with clients for Branding Projects.
- Organize and produce aesthetically pleasing PowerPoints, social media cards, and posts.

Notable Work

Reczee Behance

- Led a design project in reczee to meet the goals of the project through my designs.
- Successfully managed multiple projects simultaneously.meeting tight deadlines.

Event Maker Behance

- Event maker is created in such a manner that the visitor will not be bored while visiting our website, and the look and feel conveys everything about the party mode.
- Kept in mind that feel is more crucial for this site because it caters to the "All cool party planner guys vibe" crowd.

OrFresh **Behance**

- The platform provides clean and user-friendly visuals to keep users interested with the site.
- Transitions are designed to keep the user engaged as a visually appealing component of the design process.

daminisharma9704@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/daminisharma29/

www.behance.net/daminisharma2905

Key Skills

Wireframing

UI Design

Prototyping

User Research

Posts Design

Software

Figma

Adobe XD

Canva

VS Code

Education

M.G.M Institute of CS & IT

Bachelor's Degree in Information Technology 2018 - 2021

Pillai Collage of Art, Commerce & Science

Master's Degree in Information Technology 2021 - 2023

Certifications

- UI/UX Design
- Google UX Design •
- Introduction to Social Media Marketing
 - HTML & CSS
 - AWS Cloud Practitioner •



portfolio-2024uidesigner.streamlit.app